jcnnewswire.com 2019-05-04

# 

  1. Home
  2. Privacy Policy 

This statement discloses the privacy policies of the JCN Newswire website. JCN has adopted a set of information management guidelines, which serve as the basis for its customer relationships. Any changes to these guidelines will be posted here. 

**What information does JCN Newswire gather or track?**

JCN Newswire requires that visitors supply personal information, including name, company name, telephone number and e-mail address, prior to receiving certain corporate news and information. JCN also logs IP addresses, browser information (including navigation history) and referral information in order to improve both the design and content of its website. 

**What does JCN Newswire do with the information it gathers?**

JCN Newswire and its representatives may follow up, either by e-mail, phone or mail, with people who have downloaded information or materials from its website. Using the e-mail addresses provided at registration, NCN periodically sends promotional e-mail about new products, product enhancements and special offers. Upon request, JCN will remove any subscriber (and their personal information) from its database, allow subscribers to "opt out" of further contact, or edit/correct subscriber personal information. 

**With whom does JCN share the information it gathers or tracks?**

JCN Newswire does not release personal information about individual subscribers to outside parties. However, JCN does share personal information with its customers and global offices for the purpose of providing users with high quality, localized service. This process often includes sending the personal information across international borders. JCN is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of websites to which it is linked. 

**What security procedures are in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information under the Company's control?**

JCN Newswire operates secure data Newswires protected by industry standard firewall and SSL systems. The Company's security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary, and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by users. 

**Advertisers and Other Third Parties**

JCN Newswire contains links to other sites. The Company is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. JCN may use a third-party ad company to display ads on the website. These ads may contain cookies received with banner ads which are collected by the third-party ad company, and we do not have access to this information. The privacy practices of companies who provide services or ads through our site are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Please contact those companies directly for more information about their privacy practices. 

JCN Newswire makes every effort to ensure that personal information is treated securely and in accordance with the site's Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, the security of online data transmission cannot be guaranteed. As a result, while JCN strives to protect personal information, it cannot guarantee the security of information, and you use these services at your own risk. 

**Contacting the Website**

JCN Newswire is privately owned and run. For more information, or if you have any questions about these Terms of Use, the practices of this site or your dealings with JCN, please contact us via e-mail at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), by telephone on +81-3-5791-1821, or mail at JCN Newswire, Minami Azabu Bldg. 3F, 4-14-2 Minami Azabu, Minato-ku, Tokyo 106-0047, Japan. 

Last updated: January 2015
